$UpStage1	is No Longer Hungry and Can Sprint Normally
$UpStage3	is Well Fed and Can Sprint Longer
$UpStage4	Feels Vigorous and Has Extra Health
$UpStage5	is Fully Sated

$DownStage2	Could Eat Something
$DownStage1	is Getting Hungry
$DownStage0	is Too Hungry and Can't Knock Enemies

$Horsepower_FeedTutorial	Press the "feed" key to feed your horse on "grass" surfaces. This will provide certain buffs and remove debuffs. Keep it fed before your journeys!
$Horsepower_FeedTutorialHeader	Horsepower Feed Tutorial

$MCM_SprintInterrupt_Label	Sprint Interruption
$MCM_SprintInterrupt_Desc	Getting too slow with your horse will cause it to rear-up

$MCM_MinJumpClamp_Label	Allow Lower Jump Heights While Moving
$MCM_MinJumpClamp_Desc	By default, your minimum jump height is increased. For compatibility with other mods that lower the default jump height, keep it off unless you see other issues.

$MCM_HorseAttack_Label	Horse Attack
$MCM_HorseAttack_Desc	Make your horse attack by pressing the shout key

$MCM_SwapInput_Label	Swap Horseback Attack Inputs
$MCM_SwapInput_Desc	Left click to attack left, right click to attack right

$MCM_Petting_Label	Manual Horseback Petting
$MCM_Petting_Desc	Pet the horse with sneak key on horseback

$MCM_Graze_Label	Graze System
$MCM_Graze_Desc	Enable the hunger / grazing system. Feed your horse when on grassy surfaces with sneak key. Horses will graze on their own as well.

$MCM_SprintKnock_Label	Sprint Jump Knock
$MCM_SprintKnock_Desc	Knock actors with a sprinting jump, requires graze level 1 or above if grazing is enabled.

$MCM_HitToleration_Label	Hit Toleration
$MCM_HitToleration_Desc	Horses do a rearup after taking hits between 5-20 randomly, including spells. There's a cooldown window to prevent stunlock. The horse has to be hit, not the rider.

$MCM_AllowRagdoll_Label	Restored Ragdolls
$MCM_AllowRagdoll_Desc	Remove the "No Knockdowns" flag of the horses. Changes will take effect after the game loads another horse with the same horse race (Form ID).